http://www.texasarchive.org/privacy-policy

Effective Date: April 14, 2020
Texas Archive of the Moving Image (TAMI) has created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within our website. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website located at the URL texasarchive.org.
In order to fully understand your rights, we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy. TAMI reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our Site. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.
Information We Obtain
Individuals that sign up to receive TAMI e-communications voluntarily provide us with contact information (such as name and e-mail address). We may use this information for specific, limited purposes. You may always "opt out," either now or at any time in the future, if you do not wish to receive our messages.
Email Privacy
TAMI does not provide, sell, or rent email addresses to anyone outside the organization.
Internet Protocol Address
We collect an IP address from all visitors to our Site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Site, analyze trends, track users’ movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the site. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Use of “Cookies”
Our Site uses "cookie" messages to automatically help provide better services. They remind us who you are and your preferences for our website based on what you've done and told us before. The "cookie" is placed in your computer and is read when you come back to our website. Cookies let us track your usage of texasarchive.org, so we know which parts of our sites are most popular.
Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard. Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Site will not function properly when you view them. For more information on deleting or controlling cookies, we recommend www.AllAboutCookies.org.
Third-Party Services
We may use third-party web analytics services on our Site, such as Google Analytics. These services help us analyze how visitors use the Site. The information collected for this purpose (including your IP address and other information collected by automated means) will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers.
Google Analytics: tracks IP address information for the purpose of performance monitoring and conversion tracking.
The providers of third-party plug-ins on the Site, such as Google Maps, may use automated means to collect information regarding your use of the Site and your interactions with the plug-ins. This information is subject to the privacy policies or notices of the plug-in providers and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for these providers’ information practices. Current plug-ins used on this Site are:
Google Maps: tracks IP address information for the purpose of enabling location services, including locating nearby parking and lodging.
YouTube: tracks IP address information and Google Account information (if the user is signed into their Google Account) for the purpose of serving multimedia content.
Facebook: tracks IP address and any other account information that the user has provided to Facebook for the purpose of enabling interactive social media features and communicating upcoming events.
Twitter: tracks IP address and any other account information that the user has provided to Twitter for the purpose of enabling interactive social media features and communicating upcoming events.
We may also use third-party vendors who supply applications, payment processing, web hosting and other technologies for this Site that may have access to your personal information and anonymized information. These vendors include industry-leading payment service providers such as Amazon, Paypal, and Stripe. These vendors are prohibited from using use such information for any other purpose except to provide services in connection with this Site. We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Essentially, we encrypt all transmission of sensitive data and secure all of our repositories of data. The data transferred to our third-party payment processors when you use your credit card to make a purchase transaction with us will be transferred using SSL encryption technology to safeguard your personal information and privacy. At the vendor level, we comply with the United States payment card industry federal standards. However, you should understand that, even with the use of leading industry standards, "perfect security" cannot be guaranteed.
Security
All information provided to TAMI is transmitted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt or scramble, data before you send it to us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.
Other Websites
Our Site contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website for which TAMI may have no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites as their policies may be different than ours.
Modifications
We may amend this privacy policy from time to time; please review it periodically. We maintain the option to modify this privacy at any time by electronic notice posted on our website. Your continued use of our website after the date that such notices are posted will be deemed to be your agreement to the changed terms.
How to Contact Us with Questions
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site or your dealings with this Site, you can contact:
Texas Archive of the Moving Image (TAMI)
Open by appointment only.
